New York State Board of Mediation Cases 5581
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- A 4600 - A 4875 (1944). (Box 23)
  - United Scientific Laboratories Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 88)
  - Sani-Aqua Shower Curtains, Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 89)
  - Breakstone Bros., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 90)
  - Marseilles Hotel, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 91)
  - Stuhmer, Geo. Baking Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 92)
  - Field Baking Corp., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 93)
  - Laneri Mechanical Lab, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 94)
  - Long Island Lighting Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 95)
  - Krum, J.S., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 96)
  - Acme Quilting Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 97)
  - Hoke Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 98)
  - Schultz Sample Service, 1944 (Box 23, Folder 99)
  - Bronx and Manhattan Retail Fish Dealers Assn., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 100)
  - Winston Slipper Co., 1944 (Box 23, Folder 101)
- A 4876 - A 5199 (1944). (Box 24)
  - Amalgamated Radio and Television Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Milburt Products Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - California Pie and Baking Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - American Artists Group, The, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Frankel's, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Michaels and Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - France Sporting Goods Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Macy, R.H. and Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Sonotone Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Continental Baking Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Ledkote Products Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Shannon's Bar and Grill, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Oxford Handkerchief Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Interborough News Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Morton Coal Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Hardman, Peck and Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Ardun Mechanical Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Carol Cab Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Lowe, Joe Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Langerman Shoe Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Schenley Import Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Bergman, A. and S. Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Namm Store, The, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Polk Realty Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Machinery Builders Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Thomas, S.B. and Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Breakstone Bros., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Cairns Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Micamold Radio Corp, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Marseilles Bakery, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - United Parcel Service, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Kirchberger, M and Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Ward Baking Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Anheuser Busch Yeast Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - American Lead Pencil Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Albrecht Retail Stores, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Fadro Holding Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Jaymo Realty Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Simplicity Pattern Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Window Cleaning Employers Assn., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Ornstein, D. and Company, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - Miles Shoe Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - Rand Tea and Coffee Stores, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - Riverdale Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Interboro Furniture Mfg. Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - S and K Mfg. Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - National Backing Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - News Syndicate Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - Interborough News Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Silver Slipper, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - W. Green Electric Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Eppenbach, Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Schoonmaker, A.O. Insulation Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Triangle Thread Mills, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Waldes Koh-I-Noor, Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Fink Baking Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Blue Seal Mfg. Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - St. Francis Hotel, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Adiray Realty Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Dictograph Sales Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - Walker Engraving Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Rubico Brush Manufacturers. Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Wilson, Thomas C. Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Schoenfeld, John L. Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - Feiner, P. and Sons, Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Tishman Realty and Construction Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Ordinance Instrument Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 68)
  - Manco Bread Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Carol Cab Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 70)
  - Ledkote Products Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - United Mutual Benefit Assn., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - Bliss, E.W. Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 73)
  - Eisemann Magneto Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Baumann, C. Ludwig, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Fischer, Chas. Spring Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Peerless Hotel, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Schoonmaker, A.O. Insulation, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - Zamax Mfg. Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Luminous Processes, Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Wile, Julius and Sons, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Woolco Realty Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Benjamin Franklin Hotel, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Eagle Precision Tool and Die Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - United Cigar-Whelan Stores Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - American Lens Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - United Parcel Service, Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Modernage Furniture Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Volpit Chewing Candy Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Bee Line Bus Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Schwartz, John A., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - Union Field Cemetery, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - American Federation of Office Employees and Hotel and Club Employees, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Bohack, H.C. Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - Levy, H.S. Baking Company, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - Menon, Michael d/b/a University Show Rebuilders, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - Selectar Mfg. Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - Friedland Fixture Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - Champion Envelope Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 99)
  - Queens Borough Gas and Electric Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 100)
  - Unique Balance Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 101)
  - Oxford Handkerchief Co., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 102)
  - Doughnut Corp. of America, 1944 (Box 24, Folder 103)
  - Accmatool Corp., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 104)
  - Holmberg, A.W. and Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 24, Folder 105)
- A 5204 - A 5362 1/44-1 to 12/44-36 A 5363 - A 5450 (1944). (Box 25)
  - Chasen Bros., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Evy Slipper Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Quality Cake Baking Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Allied Master Painters Assn., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Merchants Service Bureau Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Hill Lalin and Sons, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Namm, A.I., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Allied Cleaning Contractors Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Childs Company, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Consumers Cooperative Service, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Furniture Manufacturers Assn, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Green Bus Lines, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Halpern, Gus, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Kosh, L.H. Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Austin Nichols and Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Henshaw Furniture Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Peerless Hotel, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - S and K Mfg. Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Ace Window Cleaning Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Hardman, Peck and Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Rosenberg and Antmin, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Spear and Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Columbia University, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Bloomingdale Bros., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Title Guaranty and Trust Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Zamax Mfg. Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Atlantic Macaroni Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Krasne, A., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Desco Shoe Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - United Parcel Service Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Childs Company, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, Local 404, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Cleaning Contractors Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Hathaway, W.A. and Company, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Horowitz Bros. and Margareten, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Precision Metal Products Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Briam Mfg. Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Green Bus Lines, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - United Parcel Service, In., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Rogers Diesel and Aircraft Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Confectioners Industrial Relations Board, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Federal Mogul Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Stuhmer Baking Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Stevenson Pies, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - 1871 7th Ave. Co-Op. Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Aero Spark Plug Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Associated Hotel and Residence Clubs, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Downtown Dry Goods Jobbers Assn., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Feldman Lumber Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Lorraine Fashions, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Joe Lowe Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Volk's Restaurant, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Mandel Motor Truck Exchange, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Arnold Reuben, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Sal's Millinery, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Textile Refinishers Association, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Hygrade Bag Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Maslow Bros., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - National Feather and Down Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Watch Motor Mainspring Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Barnes Development Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Broadway-Hamilton Place Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - H.C. Bohack Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Doehler Bldg., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - George C. Moore and Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - South Bay Consolidated Water Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Oritani Packaging Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Reichhold Chemical Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Einhorn's, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Ellas Baking Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - S. and W. Fine Foods, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Hellman Smoked Fish Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Dwight, Voorhis and Helmsley, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Hope's Windows, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Suburban Bus Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Unique Balance Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - Zaharoff, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - Aero Spark Plug Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - S. and S. Trucking Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - Eppenbach, inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - Atlas pipe Railing Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - The French Bootery, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 83)
  - Ulster Knife Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 84)
  - Millinery Firms: Vonnie, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 85)
  - Abbott Baking Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 86)
  - Albrechts Retail Stores Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 87)
  - Dictograph Sales Corp, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 88)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 89)
  - Williams, R.C. and Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 90)
  - Zierick Mfg. Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 91)
  - Grenlo Realty Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 92)
  - Unique Balance Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 93)
  - Interstate Appliance Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 94)
  - Longchamps Restaurants, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 95)
  - Terrytoons, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 96)
  - Queens Borough Gas and Electric Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 97)
  - Sculte Furniture Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 98)
  - Studebaker Motor Distributors, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 99)
  - United Parcel Service, inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 100)
  - Lord and Burnham Company, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 101)
  - Rhonnie's Millinery, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 102)
  - Zamax Mfg. Co., Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 103)
  - Voss Ice Machine Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 104)
  - Fairchild Camera and Instrument Corp., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 105)
  - Kozen's Pharmacy, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 106)
  - Oxford Handkerchief Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 107)
  - Ward Baking Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 108)
  - Goodfit Shoe Mfg. Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 109)
  - Piser and Company, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 110)
  - Ebling Brewing Co., Inc. and Local 56, 1944 (Box 25, Folder 111)
  - Associated Foundries and Mfg. Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 112)
  - Columbia Diamond Co., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 113)
  - Machinery Builders, Inc., 1944 (Box 25, Folder 114)
- A 5451 - A 5154 (1945). (Box 26)
  - National Vacuum Cleaner Supply Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Orgler Envelope Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Ridgewood Pie Baking Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Spear Box Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Le Cody Toasted Pies, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Ludwig Baumann and Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Raab, Paul, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Levy, Henry S. and Sons, Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Spear and Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - American Lead Pencil Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Dictograph Products Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Rokeach, I. and Sons, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Cairns Corp., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Hardman, Peck and Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Bliss, E.W., Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Liquidometer corp., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Marlon Confections Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Krasdale Foods, Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Kresge, S.S. Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Pressman, J. and Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Doig, William S., Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Hudson American Corp., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Salwen, Joe Paper Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Gissinger, Oscar, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Krasdale Foods Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Krasne Bros., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Commercial Cable Co., The, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Bloomingdale Bros. Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - 1945 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Somers Associates, Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - A.A. Contracting CO., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Esmeo Auto Products Corp., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Mutual Paper Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Queens Machine Corp., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Textile Jobbers Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Ford Instrument Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Purity Bakeries, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Nathan Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Reber, John Baking Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - American Cystoscope Makers Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Ludwig Baumann, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - 65th Street Corp., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - United Parcel Service Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Royal Switchboard Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Avenue "H" Corp., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Electronics Corp. of America, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - Russell Lofts, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Finkel, J., Distributing Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Scarsdale Bus Company, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Hotel Wayne, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Boettcher, A.W., Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Friedland Fixture Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Rollson, Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - 511 West 232nd Street, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Radio Wire and Television Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Eastern Cooperative Wholesale Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - Yonkers Bus Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Associated Foundries and Manufacturers., Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Krasne Bros., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - Peckman, J. and Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - Wagner Pie Baking Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - Accurate Brass Company, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - Mannequin Display Studio, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - Copperman, Nathan, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - Friedland Fixture Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - Blumstein L.M., Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - Kamen Products Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - Continental Baking Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - Finkel, J. Distributing Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Marlow Floral Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 71)
  - Manufacturers Machine and Tool Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 72)
  - Advertisers Broadcasting Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 73)
  - Berlin and Jones, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 74)
  - Dictograph Sales Corp., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 75)
  - Klein Piano Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 76)
  - Associated Bias Manufacturers, Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 77)
  - Zyloware Corp., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 78)
  - Bommer Spring Hinge Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 79)
  - Reynolds, R.J., Tobacco Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 80)
  - Associated Foundries Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 81)
  - Rapaport, Alexander, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 82)
  - Reuben, Arnold, Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 83)
  - Treo Mattress Company, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 84)
  - Copperman, Nathan, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 85)
  - Janaug, Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 86)
  - Miele, Humbert, Estate of, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 87)
  - Playette Footwear, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 88)
  - Hudson American Corp., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 89)
  - Kayser, Julius and Company, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 90)
  - Franklin Simon and Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 91)
  - Kurschner Baking Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 92)
  - Machinery Builders, Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 93)
  - Hudson American Corp., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 94)
  - 222 Riverside Drive (Dooley and Collard), 1945 (Box 26, Folder 95)
  - Accmatool Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 96)
  - Michaels and Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 97)
  - Bertro Tool and Die Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 98)
  - 1821 Bryant Avenue and 2504 Bronx Park East, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 99)
  - Henshaw Furniture Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 100)
  - Clinton Hotel, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 101)
  - Ermold, Edward, Co., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 102)
  - Dreier, M., 1945 (Box 26, Folder 103)
- A 5755 - A 6077 (1945). (Box 27)
  - Friedland Fixture Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Greenstone, AL., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Atlantic Macaroni Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Zierick Mfg. Corp., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Copperman, Nathan, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Feiner, P. and Sons, Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Silberman and Intrata, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Barclay Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Grand Novelty Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - S. Modern Stamping Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - New York Fruit and Produce Purveyors Assn., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Ansley Radio Corp., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Hudson American Corp., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Accmatool Corp., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - American House Craft Corp. and others., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Daniels and Kennedy, Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Longchamps Restaurants, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Waldes Koh-I-Noo, Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Korman, Murray, Studio, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Marseillaise French Baking Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Swiss American Watch Hospital, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Stevenson Pie Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Strauss Fasteners Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - General Baking Company, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - National Processed Foods Corp., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Ward Leonard Electric CO., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Taft Barber Shop, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Lampert, Irving, Company, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Modernage Furniture Corp., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Champs Elysees, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Liquidometer Corp., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Ermold, Edward, Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Queens Borough Gas and Electric CO., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Gnome Bakers Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Queens County Jockey Club, et al., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Hardman, Peck and Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Lewro Theatre Corp., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Solar Precision Castings, Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Walter Motor Truck Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Zatlin's Curtain Store, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Precision Metal Products Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - California Pie Baking Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - 1801 Bryant Avenue, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Frucht, Jack, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Queens Borough Gas and Electric Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Goldsmith Bros, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 46)
  - Ideal Leather Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 47)
  - Reeves-Ely Laboratories Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 48)
  - W.G. Wagner and Sons, Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 49)
  - Gottesman Pharmacy, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Gussack Machined Products, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Kurtz, J. and Sons, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 52)
  - Plazmont Pharmacy, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 53)
  - Schenider, M., Company, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 54)
  - Gelman's Hosiery Shop, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 55)
  - Fleisig, A. and Sons, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 56)
  - Remington Optical CO., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 57)
  - Levy, H.S. and Sons, Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 58)
  - Daniels and Kennedy Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 59)
  - Broadway Chromium Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 60)
  - Norsid Company, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 61)
  - Selectar Mfg. Corp., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 62)
  - Champion Envelope Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 63)
  - Dependable Diamond Cutters, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 64)
  - Morey Machinery Co., Inc, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 65)
  - 68 West 138th Street, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 66)
  - Anchor Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 67)
  - Friedland Fixture Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 68)
  - Gottfried Baking Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 69)
  - Swiss American Watch Hospital, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 70)
  - Cabol Cab Corp., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 71)
  - 89 Fairview Avenue, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 72)
  - Willow Cab Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 73)
  - California Pie and Baking Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 74)
  - Barclay Mfg. Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 75)
  - Desco Shoe Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 76)
  - Vogel, Paul Hardware Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 77)
  - Storms, H.M., Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 78)
  - Wigods, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 79)
  - Allied Cleaning Contractors Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 80)
  - Atlantic Macaroni Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 81)
  - Friedland Fixture CO., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 82)
  - Acme Window Display Service, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 83)
  - Dri-Wear Fur Processing Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 84)
  - Bloomingdales Bros. Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 85)
  - Olympic Pharmacy, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 86)
  - Macy, R.H. and Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 87)
  - Lord and Burnham Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 88)
  - Manger Hotels, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 89)
  - Candy Industry Board of Trade, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 90)
  - Jack Dooda's Luncheonette, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 91)
  - Merchants Refrigerating Co., 1945 (Box 27, Folder 92)
  - Champion and Metal Products, 1945 (Box 27, Folder 93)
- A 6078 - A 6269 and 1/45-1 to 5/46-8 (1945-46). (Box 28)
  - Childs Company, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Displaywell, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Kitty Kelly Shoes, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - R.K. Baking Corp, et al., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Thomas, S.B. Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Bloomingdale Bros., Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Dinhofer Corp., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - 3554 Rochambeau Avenue, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Scope and Contents
    `
  - Bond Mark Cigar Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Kelton Cosmetic Co., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - La Rosa, V., and Sons, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - North Shore Bus Co., Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Topps Hosiery, Inc., 1945 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Restaurant Crillon, 1945 (Box 28, Folder 14)